(Leonard:)Sheldon, dinner's here.
SHELDON:
Tandoori Palace?
(Leonard:)No, we went somewhere new.
(Sheldon:)You're good-naturedly ribbing me,
aren't you?
(Leonard:)No, look, Mumbai Palace.
(Sheldon:)Why? Why would we change?
(Sheldon:)We had a perfectly good palace.
Tandoori Palace is our palace.
(Leonard:)Trust me, this will be just fine.
(Howard:)You are the authority on just fine.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
(Leonard:)What's that supposed to mean?
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)Exactly. Not bad, but not great.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
(Penny:)-What are they talking about?
-I don't know.
(Sheldon:)-I know. As I'm sure you're aware--
-Dut! Dut-dut-dut-dut!
(Sheldon:)If that's Morse code, that's terrible.
(Sheldon:)As I was saying, you and Leonard
had a disappointing sexual encounter.
(Sheldon:)Earlier this evening,
Leonard characterized it as, "Just fine."
So, what you're seeing is a continuation
of the mocking that followed.